Yesterday, I hung out at Tohru's place for the first time.
Remy needs detailed stat!
What you're imagining definitely didn't happen, so calm down.
I learned he's got a massive TV and enough spare rooms to house a small village on the second and third floors.
I thought he was a bar club like me!
Um, my condolences.
What's going on?
Hush, you stupid rich asshole!
What the hell could I do?
I'll go ahead and pre-order a cake after all.
Our shop doesn't really do pre-orders, but for you, I think we'll make an exception.
Can't have Christmas without a cake.
So, what kind do you want?
One with tons of whipped cream globbed on, sounds great!
Okay!
I asked Yuna to spend Christmas with us!
So then with Yuna and Miyamura, that brings the headcount up to six.
Wait, is he even gonna make it?
He better, so make sure you invite him!
It's cool if you wanna skip out, but it just wouldn't be Christmas without Miyamura.
You want Christmas? Then go sleep in a manger!
Man, wish I could.
But starting the 23rd, I'll probably be busy helping out at the shop.
Yeah, figured as much.
Though, if I can, I'll try and stop by for a minute.
No, it's cool if you don't have time.
Our celebration is pretty much done once dinner's over.
I'm sorry.
No!
How can you not spend the holiday with us, Miyamura?
Well, you know, it's just the time of your baked goods are in high demand.
You have to come over!
Please, bro!
I'll be sad if you don't!
Sota, don't make this even harder.
But, bro!
Forgive me!
Come back!
Call me when you get home!
All I want for Christmas is you, bro!
You know he's dating me, right?
Hey!
Miyamura!
No!
Maybe he's dating me.
cookies
for Christmas is you, bro!
昏 그렇죠
Me
If I remember if I hear something,
I could make.
Like I!
Oh, ya!
I'll see you next time.
Shikawa, no denying we crossed the friendship line, but I think it's still too soon to date her.
Huh?
Uh...
I was under the impression they were dating.
I knew you dumb jerks would react like that!
I don't know why, but I thought you two would think I thought they were dating without even
thinking to properly consult me!
If you don't stop with all your thinking, your thoughts will give us an aneurysm!
You thought we thought?
One of the matter is that we're not dating.
So what, do you not like her like that?
I do like her!
Wow, it takes a confident man to yell that out loud.
It's this weird limbo, but it's where we are.
I wouldn't say that it's weird.
A little surprising, sure.
But, like, who cares what we think?
The only opinion that really matters in this situation is Yoshikawa's.
The important thing is if you two are happy with your current relationship, and more power
to you if you are.
It's not my place to say that how you label it is right.
Guys, what's wrong?
Teach me to be cool like you.
Just leave it to the master of romance to tell you exactly what you need to hear.
How'd I suddenly become the master of romance?!
Aha! I finally found you!
You mind if I hang at your place today?
Hm?
I want to finish that game we started before.
You do? That's fine by me.
Let's beat it together.
Uh...
Actually, we better not.
Oh, okay. You have plans?
Well, not plans, per se.
It's because of something else.
You know what? Never mind.
You can come.
It's fine. I can take a rain check, Toadu.
There's no need. It was gonna happen sooner or later.
I'll never get used to this.
It's just so huge.
I'm home.
Why do you feel quiet?
Just being a little more careful with the doors, and let's go upstairs.
Come on, hurry!
Soft footsteps. That's it.
Geez, why is this dang hallway so freaking long?
Oh.
Maybe his parents are home and he doesn't want me to meet them.
Would it really be the end of the world if that happened?
Sorry for rushing you. You're a real one.
I wish I were a hot guy.
I wouldn't have to jump through hoops like that.
Huh?
What hoops? What are you talking about? I'm glad you're a girl.
But if I were a boy...
Whoa, hey!
Was that quite the sound of the door locking?
That's not a problem, is it?
AHHHHH!
Why the heck are you taking your clothes off?
I'm not!
The only thing that I'm taking off is my tie, because it's what I always do.
AHHHHH!
Yoshikawa...
A little better?
Could have sworn you knew, but I'm far from a creep.
If you're going to spend time with me, then the last thing I want you to feel is uneasy.
I didn't cross my mind till she panicked.
No, it's fine.
I'm sorry. Of course I'm comfortable around you, because why wouldn't I be?
Oh, um, that's good.
Yeah, good.
Good.
That's you, Toadu?
AHHHHH!
Crap! The door!
Huh?
Hey, why are you trying to shut me out?
Do you have a friend over?
Yup, gonna chill and play a video game!
Nothing you need to come in here for!
Wait, this woman...
Is she your mother?
At least let me get the two of you some drinks!
We're okay!
The butt's saying it's over, my guy!
Why are you acting like this in front of a guest?
You know, if I shouldn't be here, I can still take that rain check.
Yoshikawa, no! Stay put! You are right where you need to be!
K!
So, her name's Yoshikawa?
Are you in the mood for some cake?
Um, sure!
Let me go grab you a slice bit.
Hey, I told you we were good.
Who is this charming, vivacious, Amazonian woman?
It'll be the work of a minute, okay?
Fine.
But not when you come back so we have a little warning, would ya?
Hey, that cake isn't gonna serve itself, so you better hop to it!
Funny how quickly you change your tune!
Is that your mom?
Thankfully, no.
She just helps out around the house from time to time.
Name's Yashiro.
And she loves bombarding me with questions about you.
She'll be like,
Who were you walking with the other day, Toru?
Or,
Your mother told me you had a girl over, Toru!
It's like she has this weird sixth sense.
Toru?
Who were you talking about?
I know you didn't just barge in here without knocking now!
Whoops.
Guess I did.
So cheesecake isn't the only kind we have.
There's shortcake as well.
I'll take the short...
No.
Cheesecake sounds good.
Mm-hmm.
A friendly reminder.
Your mom's on speed dial.
Hands to yourself, young man.
Oh, please.
You actually think I'd pull something knowing you're in the next room?
Holler if you kids need anything.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry.
She's just acting extra annoying because she finally got a chance to meet you.
She's nice, I swear.
Oh, cool.
You actually think I'd pull something knowing you're in the next room?
So if Yashiro wasn't in the next room, what would he try to pull?
Yoshikawa?
What did you have for lunch that's making you act so jumpy?
You okay?
Yes, and my lunch was normal.
Gosh.
Hey, don't stare.
You know that is beyond rude.
So, how about that video game?
Great.
We'll definitely beat it today.
Oh, know what?
Might help if it's plugged in, huh?
I'm happy.
I like things the way they are.
This bakery's cakes are fantastic.
Wait till you try.
It's from Yamura's shop.
Sengoku.
Hey, Reppy.
What the hell, dude?
Sorry.
So, um, just making sure, but you're coming for Christmas, aren't you?
Because I mean, it's Christmas, so why wouldn't you?
Right?
We could spend it at my place.
I'd prefer my place, so please come.
Oh, thanks.
Do you not have a heart?
She's in tears because of you.
There you go.
Let it all out.
I would've thought he'd say no.
Miyamura!
I think this calls for one of your signature headbutts!
You got it.
Guys, let's hear his side of the story first.
I have a good reason for declining.
You would, too, if you knew what she keeps in her house.
I'd rather not disgust if given the choice, but here goes!
Home sweet home!
The mantis stares at me!
His beauty eyes think so much!
Those don't belong to Remy!
Every last one of them is her father's!
She can take them down if they freak you out!
The mantis?
You should've got your grades at the assembly today.
May I see?
Look, our little brainiac managed to score an A in every subject except Art and P.E.
Of course she did! She's a smarty-pants like her old man!
Let's see.
I suppose she does take after you in math.
Hope the similarities stop there.
Then why would you hope that?
This must be such an emotional moment for you.
Why?
I believe I asked a question first.
You're a third year, Kyoko.
The next time you receive your grades, you'll be getting a diploma.
That's right.
Once April rolls around, I won't be in high school anymore.
I got my report card, too!
Wow!
Great job, buddy!
I got a perfect hundred-
This time next year, what will my life look like?
After graduation, what am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
I got it right in front of your face!
You're not even looking at it, are you?
I was happy about your grades!
You just said she takes after me seconds ago!
I've been working hard all year and was excited to share!
Knock it off!
Thank you!
Happy holidays!
That is one big Christmas tree.
Looking up too much makes you lose perspective.
Oh, you're Yoshikawa's sister, right?
You don't have your glasses on.
How did you know?
I made the switch over to contacts fairly recently.
Oh, you don't say.
I've avoided them for years, but maybe I should finally give them a try.
I'll buy them for you if you'd like.
We could go right now.
What?
Why?
Because it's Christmas.
That's why.
It's still a little strange for a high school kid to buy a college student contacts.
Isn't that also why you're dressed up?
Not quite.
I was interviewing for potential jobs.
I try to get money and work.
Yuki tries to goof off.
You're laughing because it's true and we're both well aware.
So please don't hold back on my account.
Dumb baby sis.
Yeah.
That wasn't why I...
Oh, dear.
All right.
Let's take home, shall we?
Oh, wow.
This line of...
Why are you watching this?
You want something sweet?
No.
You make a better door than a window, you know.
It's kind of hard to see the screen.
That means move.
I don't care if you're sick or my brother.
If you talk like that to me again, you're dead.
And put your nasty tissues in the trash, dumbass.
That's what I've been doing, but Kiko keeps taking them out and playing with them.
Yeah, right.
Huh?
You made me miss it.
You think you can put the books down long enough to eat dinner?
Oh, of course.
That's our food?
You went all out!
Come on, Sengoku.
You can endure a few bugs for Remy's sake, right?
She said you agreed to meet up with her at 7 o'clock.
It's 6.30, so you can still make it.
Will you be spending Christmas by yourself, Sakura?
Considering I'm Buddhist, yes.
Same as every year.
Guess I'll get going.
You are doing so well!
It's no use.
I can't hold down a meal with those creepy crawlies around.
Remember, you're having dinner with Remy, not the insects.
I could always repeat a year and stay back with you.
Or on second thought, you could hurry up and graduate.
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Wait for me.
One more year.
Just 365 days to go.
We've been through this!
He has to work, so he couldn't be here.
Yeah, but it's your job to force him to come anyway.
It's my job to compromise his livelihood?
Although, he is going to stop by and drop off our cake.
Ha, now we're talking.
Do you think he'll have time to come in for a bit?
No.
He'll probably just say hi, bye, and leave.
Aww.
Mom, if you're bummed on my behalf, I'm not sad!
Then you're on your own, because we're all very sad about it.
Huh?!
Um, Kyoko?
Oh, thank you, Yuna.
It's from Miyamorta.
Oh, it's a Christmas miracle!
Merry Christmas, guys.
You're here!
Come play cards!
It's really fun.
What if I could, but they still need me at the shop.
Damn, your hands must be freezing!
Get in here and warm up!
I'll fix you something hot to drink!
Um, okay, but I gotta down it and go.
Yes!
We can play a round of Old Maid!
This is a whole lot different from last year.
I, uh, really do have to get going now.
Aww!
Hey!
Don't awe him!
I'm sorry.
I'm gonna go walk him back to the bakery, and I better not see any of you following us.
Huh?
You're sure?
It's cold out.
I'm coming!
It's just snow and ice.
Everything gets so quiet when it snows.
Guess Hori's affected by it, too.
We'll be high school grads pretty soon.
That we will.
But it's still months away.
Come to think of it?
Miyamoto,
I still don't know you.
Not as well as I'd like to.
I feel like I've barely scratched the surface.
So listen, Hori.
When it comes to knowing the real you,
I feel like I've barely scratched the surface.
But that's okay.
We'll have time even after we graduate.
Because I…
I still want to be with you.
Well,
as long as you feel the same way,
which I hope you do.
I still want to be with you.
So, um…
Could you please say something?
Okay.
Will you marry me,
Kyokuhori?
You idiot.
On that note…
I swear to the moon and back,
I'll make you happy.
What?
I'm letting you know if you make me your wife,
I'll make you the happiest man,
not only on this planet,
but the next.
Wait…
I should be the one telling you that.
It wouldn't make sense for you to say it.
I'm the self-centered one,
so I'd have to make a conscious effort
to put your happiness before my own.
You know it's true.
So you can't tell me that stuff.
Well, I don't think that's how it works,
but who am I to argue?
Never proposed before.
I look forward to our future together.
Hopefully it'll be a good one.
Right.
Yes.
On my way.
I really gotta book it back now.
Oh, sure.
Be safe.
It's so cold.
I better get going, too.
At least my face is warm.
Mmm.
It's so cold.
I will help-
See you next time.
気付いた冬の朝が約束するよ 近くにいるから 見れないものほど 大事にするよ 言葉にできないんだけどね
気付いた冬の朝が約束するよ 気付いた冬の朝が約束するよ
気付いた冬の朝が約束するよ
どうぞ
If there's no crowd.
But we made it this far.
Come on, let's do this!
So, what's your fortune say?
Uh, remain calm amidst the storm and keep moving forward.
You're kidding. There has to be more than that.
I think it's fine.
I have your smile on my life, and that's enough to keep me calm and moving forward.
What? I couldn't hear you over the crowd.
Didn't say anything.
No?
Nope. Must have been the wind.
Well, for your info, I also get inspired by your smile.
It makes me happy.
So you did hear me?
What was that?
It's kind of a weird concept.
You're gonna be the very last person I see this year.
But you'll be the first one I see as soon as the new year starts. Wild.
I guess you're right.
And you know what else?
I hope every year we'll be like this from now on.
Huh.
Hey, Lea Morda.
Hmm?
Do you think we'll be together forever?
I know we will.
Forever.
Got it.
euchneesaiisisisisis.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Bye.